Hello friends, ICICI Lombard
's quarter one earnings have been declared for Szechwan.
In this video, we will
see a detailed analysis of ICICI Lombard's quarter one earnings.
Apart from this, we will see a comparison of the quarter on quarter performance of these numbers.
Friends, Vineyard is spread all over the world
and in India too,
business is very
important due to the combination personnel. So, I will try to convey
to you some of the main points of the market commentary related to the challenge faced by the Allahabad management in running the business during the combination pandemic.
So
friends, if you have
not subscribed to my channel yet, then please
subscribe to my channel and press the bell icon so
that
whatever news related to the stock market that I post on my channel, you keep getting it
updated. So
friends, let's start this video now.
Friends, the number which is
long in type, as we know, or such a group has a
business which is the
business of insurance companies, so their Dharamkot  If we
look at the comparison of the numbers of and, then
in the April to June quarter of last year i.e. why
and in 2020, they had registered a total income of 2768 82
crores, which has increased to 2832 crores in the
April to June quarter of this year i.e. 2021, that is, there has been an
increase of almost eight percent in the total income,
friends, whereas if we talk about net profit, then even
longer than last year, where a
net profit of Rs 310 crores was registered in the quarter,
this year i.e.
in the April to June quarter of 2021, it has been successful in registering a net profit of 38 crores with an
increment of 28.5 percent in such a length, so
friends, from the comparison of Pot and researchers,
sorry,
from the Amazon of Scotland researchers, it is clear
that the ICC number, its result, is
compared to last year's quarter,
except for the opposition, this obscene combination of
pandemic and if kept in mind, then it is showing a very
good growth chop.
So friends, some more important takeaways of this company, since
becoming its headquarter, let
me tell you that its
direct premium was 200 crores. The GDPI
of this company has increased by 5.3 percent compared to last year.
Last year, where the unit total GDP was registered, it had registered 3302 crores,
whereas this year these people were able to
register 3302 crores on GDP. Friends, if we
leave out the crop statement, then on these black flags, it is
seen that it has redeemed more.
Compared to last year, the
department has increased by 6.2 percent. If we
leave out the provident insurance business,
we know that the
list of affected businesses is industries,
one of them is agriculture industry, so let's
remove the etc. statement as well.
Now they have seen a huge decline
in GDPI from last year, there was a
decline of 60 percent in the quarter ended June
and up to this the total GDP was reduced to 3333274 crores. If we
leave out the drops element, then
friends, the insurance
companies  The combine thresher whose license was suspended was
Next Nine 70% Inverter One of
Sciences So a complete 210 percent in
quarter and nurses spider med spider
losses increased you to sour trophy vents
Friends I know that in India
in the last quarter Aman and Nishan were
from two cycles so because of that 20
insurance companies reached a lot of places
but about that I told that the amount
Bindeshwar 98.4 percent in q1 fi
twenty20 so excluding the impact
of cycle as per village of rupees 331
crores compared to 98.7 percent in doctors
and nurses stored in the impact of
cycle Hanif that 6 crore company set Friends I
know that in the quarter of 2020 there was
a circular named Funny which
hit the bus stand sides of India
and hit the students of India so at
that time if the impact of Funny was there then
it should be removed for this year  If the
impact is
removed by marking it quickly, then the price of combine thresher is 98.4
percent. Such a number. Solvency for the company is
yes to front part time set June
30th August 2017 times at March 30th
more than minimum Mriga requirement of 1.5
times newspaper means in the last
quarter for nurses, their
solvency issue was 2.17 times and this
time in the card of one week, in the June 2016
quarter, their solvency rate was
2.5 times. So friends, this is the
details of Lombard's quarter one judge. That's all for
today.
If you guys want a video of any benefit you got from this company, then
definitely tell me in the comment,
I will definitely make it. If you liked the video, then do
not forget to subscribe to this channel
and definitely like and share this video.
Thank you.